hi guys this is Scott from helpful
Solutions and welcome to my in-depth
review of credential life insurance make
sure to watch until the end of the video
to know my final verdict of whether it
is worth it let's start with a brief
overview credential offers 13 policies
within its life insurance plans to fit
your situation to buy insurance locate a
credential life insurance agent in your
state alternatively visit
www.prudential.com select insurance from
the navigation bar Tap life insurance
and click the contact me button to fill
out a contact form so an agent can get
in touch the link is in the description
Prudential life insurance stands out for
its multiple policy options the
following are what I thought were the
main pros and cons pros Prudential has
excellent Financial strength ensuring it
will pay claims for a long time the
company's website is userfriendly and
provides clear illustrations of its
insurance policies Prudential Life
Insurance insurance has flexible income
requirements cons the company's term
Life policies are costly credential
doesn't provide 247 customer support
which might be inconveniencing for most
working customers now let's look at some
of the main features that make it stand
out from the rest Prudential offers more
policies Prudential offers 13 policies
within their term Universal and whole
life insurance plans these policies let
you customize your plan to fit your situ
situation in contrast Trans America
offers six policies within its life
insurance plans which some may find
restricting a higher C off age for new
customers Prudential allows customers up
to age 85 to sign up for select life
insurance policies for instance you can
get the pr term one and PR life
essential UL policies if you're 85 years
old in contrast Guardian Life
Insurance's cut off age for new
customers is 75 years which blcks out
older customers so the following are who
it is best suited for customers over 60
who are struggling to find affordable
life insurance coverage visa and green
card holders who don't have a Social
Security number My overall verdict
Prudential life insurance is an
affordable option for customers over 60
Alik the company's higher cof
application age decent policy choices
and accessibility to immigrants however
I'd like credential to introduce 24-hour
customer support and to review its term
life policy prices nevertheless
credential is worth exploring if you're
in the market for life insurance please
note that these rates are current and
may change in the future thanks for
watching